Pitchayakit Pahamak Software Engineer

Last update: October 9, 2021

The online version is available at https://pitchayakit.github.io/cv

Residence

Bangkok, Thailand

Phone

**** +66831225471

GitHub

opitchayakit

Email

<u>pitchayakit.p@gmail.com</u>

Laravel	++++	PHP	++++	SCSS	++++	jQuery	++++	Boostrab	++++	Tailwind	++++
WordPress	++++	Resful	++++	GIT	++++	SQL	++++	С	++++	AlpineJs	+++
VueJs	+++	NodeJs	+++	Linux	+++	Python	++				

Over 5 years of software development career in a variety of companies including startup and digital agency. I graduated with a Master's degree in Network Learning Technology, NCU, Taiwan. I has been working on both back-end and front-end website development. Moreover, I am intersted in IoT and Machine learning. Please get in touch

Professional Experience

Lexicon

2020 - prosent

- Managed up Line CRM system
- · Managed up CMS using Laravel and WordPress
- · Electric search
- · Data migration
- · Coaching internships in web development and technical support

Laravel WordPress VueJS Nova Alpine JS

Freelancer

2018 - 2020

- Managed up to 5 company websites
- Managed up to 2 E-commerce websites
- · 1 library website for searching books using Laravel

WordPress Laravel

Empag

2017 - 2018

- · Coaching internships in web development and technical support
- Managed up to 4 web content management systems and tasks at a given time
- Collaborate with designer in order to ensure quality and accuracy of the designy
- A Support tool for web scraping and export to excel file

WordPress NodeJs

Onestockhome

Mar 2017 - Sep 2017

• Migration content management system to Ruby on Rail platform

- · Developed front-end website using jQuery, Boostrap, HTML and CSS in Ruby on Rail platform
- Supported the use of content management system and improve user interface

Ruby on Rail React

Rippleworkz

2016 - 2017

- Integrated HTML to WordPress and Prestashop
- Managed up to 4 webs content management system and tasks at a given time.
- Collaborate with project manager to develop website, which is beyond own management project

| WordPress | jQuery |

SeSaMe (Sensor-enhanced Social Media) Center, National University of Singapore

Jul 2015 - Dec 2015

- SENSE video analytics web application replaced video output for detection, tracking and counting by HTML Canvas
- Take over and developed SeSaMe website using Joomla CMS

Play Framework | HTML Canvas | Joomla | OpenCV

Education

Master of Network Learning Technology, College of Electrical Engineering & Computer Science, National Central University, Taiwan [2018 - 2020]

Bachelor of Computer Engineering, College of Engineering, Kasetsart University, Thailand [2013 - 2016]

Additional Experience

A Study of using IoT and Zenbo robot to facilitate students' interaction in flipped classroom and the analysis of their perception.

[loT][Zenbo][Machine learning]

Smart home with door and light control System.

IoT PHP JQuery